media-freaks.com 2008-06-27

# Mediafreaks | 3D Animation

|    
---  

About Mediafreaks  
  
Mediafreaks Projects  
  
Animation for Documentaries  
  
Animated Commercials  
  
Medical Animation  
  
Architectural Animation  
  
Motion Graphics  
  
Cartoon Series  
  
Contact Mediafreaks  

Inhouse Animation Projects   

Character Licensing   
  
Katakune  
  
Sedo Dog  
  
Red Cap & Friends  
  
Happy School Friends   
  
Candy Box  
  
Tie Jing   
  
  | 

**MEDIAFREAKS PTE LTD INTERNET PRIVACY POLICY**

**Last Modified**   
This Policy was last modified on January 1, 2008. 

**Introduction**   
A key player in the animation industry in Singapore, MEDIAFREAKS PTE LTD is an **animation production company** that focuses on working closely with producers, distributors, broadcasters and partners worldwide to produce original television content and high-end animation for broadcast and marketing purposes. 

MEDIAFREAKS PTE LTD is committed to respecting your privacy, and we have created this privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”) to give you a clear understanding of how our Web Site operates, and how personally identifiable information is handled.    
We have a clear Privacy Policy: we collect no personally identifiable information through this web site unless you voluntarily supply it.  We define personally identifiable information as information that can uniquely identify an individual person.   
This privacy statement explains under what circumstances we gather personal information, how we use it, your choices in regard to our use of the information and how we protect the information.   
By using our Web Site, you consent to the collection and use of information as set forth in this Privacy Policy.   
Please note that this Privacy Policy applies only to online activities. 

**Type of Information Collected**

When you visit our Web Site, we may collect and store information from you that you voluntarily choose to give us or enter on our Web Site, including personally identifiable information.  In these instances, we will obtain your consent.  Our primary purposes in collecting and processing your personally identifiable information are to provide you with the services you request or to personalize product information and offers for you.  If you request us to do so, we will use your information to provide you with additional information about our products and services and to send you information on other products and services that may be of interest to you. If so, we will state this in the area of our Web Site where we collect information for these purposes. 

**Our Use of the Information**

If you need to provide personal information to access features or services, we will clearly disclose how the information will be used.   
We do not sell, trade, or rent your personally identifiable information to others. However, we may share your personally identifiable information with other MEDIAFREAKS PTE LTD businesses or affiliates, our agents, contractors or business partners in order that they may perform services for us. For example, your personally identifiable information may be shared (i) with contractors we use to support our business ( _e.g._ fulfillment services, technical support, delivery services, and financial institutions), (ii) in connection with the sale, assignment, or other transfer of the business of this site to which the information relates, or (iii) where required by applicable laws, court orders, or government regulations.  

In addition, since we conduct research on user demographics, interests, and behaviors based upon information provided to us during use of our Web Sites, we may combine your information with information collected from other individuals to produce anonymous, aggregated, and statistical information. Aggregated and statistical data does not include personally identifiable information. We use this information, such as the percentage of male or female visitors, or the percentage of visitors within certain age brackets, to improve the content of our site. We also may share this anonymous aggregated or statistical information, which does not identify particular individuals nor associate particular individuals with illnesses or conditions, with partners or other third parties.   
As our company changes and grows, we might sell or buy companies, subsidiaries, products or assets. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. In the event MEDIAFREAKS PTE LTD goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its products or assets, your personal information will likely be transferred.  We will make every effort to notify you via e-mail, letter or public posting of any such change in the control of your personal information. At the time of our notification, you will be given a clear choice to allow the use of your personal information for secondary purposes such as product information, research, promotions, discounts and other legally valid business communications. 

**Notice**

Where MEDIAFREAKS PTE LTD collects personally identifiable information directly from individuals, we inform them about the purpose and use of the collected information, and the choices and means, if any, we offer individuals for limiting the use and disclosure of their personal information. Notice is provided in clear and conspicuous language when individuals are asked for the information.  MEDIAFREAKS PTE LTD does not use or disclose the information for a purpose other than that for which it was originally collected. 

**Consent**

MEDIAFREAKS PTE LTD believes that consent is one of the most important privacy principles. You have the choice not to submit any personally identifiable information to us (although under such circumstances you would be unable to participate in all aspects of our Web Site).   
On the enrollment page where you register for e-mail distribution or other services, an “opt-in” mechanism is provided, meaning that you will not receive communications or services from us unless you click the box expressing your explicit consent. For certain communications and services, we verify your explicit consent prior to commencing the requested service.  If later you choose to end the communications or services from us you can do so by changing your previously indicated choice in the relevant web site, or, in case of e-mail distributions, each e-mail message we send you provides a link to unsubscribe from the e-mail list for that particular service or distribution. 

**Access to Review, Correct, and Delete Information**

MEDIAFREAKS PTE LTD uses personally identifiable information only in ways that are compatible with your consent and the purposes for which it was collected.  We take reasonable steps to ensure that personal information is relevant to its intended use, accurate, complete, and current.  

**Security**

We are committed to the security of personally identifiable information and we take reasonable precautions to maintain that protection.   
MEDIAFREAKS PTE LTD has implemented SSL technology to protect the transmission of personally identifiable information. This technology encrypts the information prior to transmission over the Internet between your computer and our servers.  While MEDIAFREAKS PTE LTD has implemented SSL technology for some purposes, we cannot guarantee the privacy of all transmissions (including, e-mail communications) to and from our Web Sites.  We protect personally identifiable information stored on the web site servers from unauthorized access using reasonable technical and procedural controls. 

Although MEDIAFREAKS PTE LTD uses physical and administrative procedures to attempt to safeguard personally identifiable information, we cannot guarantee that it is completely secure from people who might attempt to evade security measures or intercept transmissions over the Internet. 

**Cross-border Data Transfer**

The collection, use, and disclosure of personally identifiable information discussed in this policy may involve a transfer of the information to jurisdictions located outside your country of residence that may not have equivalent laws and rules regarding privacy and data protection.  In these cases, we will ask for your consent to such transfers and disclosures in accordance with this policy. 

**Retention of Personally Identifiable Information**

Once you have provided personally identifiable information to MEDIAFREAKS PTE LTD, we store and maintain the information you have volunteered for so long as we need it to provide the service that you requested, unless you have directed us otherwise, or for so long as we are required by law. 

**Cookies**

Cookies are tokens of information that our web sites may provide to your browser, which is used only by our web sites while you are at those sites.  The MEDIAFREAKS PTE LTD sites supply your web browser with cookies that contain a unique identifier used to better understand web site usage in the aggregate so that we know what areas of our site users prefer ( _e.g._ , based on the number of visits to those areas).       
MEDIAFREAKS PTE LTD will only be able to read those cookies that we place; we cannot access or read other parties’ cookies.  We may also use cookies on an aggregate basis to track site navigation and traffic trends. This aggregated and anonymous information will help us to improve Site content, and may be shared with partners or other third parties.    
If you are a registered user on the MEDIAFREAKS PTE LTD web site, when you login, we may supply you with a cookie that is maintained by your browser and contains your identifier.  This type of cookie is used to identify you and provide you with access to areas of our web site that are limited to registered users, such as those that allow you to view and manage your account. 

If you simply want to browse, you do not have to accept cookies from our site.  Should you decide, however, that you would like to register and login to special areas of the web site and you have modified your browser settings not to accept the cookies, you will need to re-set your browser to accept cookies that we send it. Otherwise, we will not be able to let you participate in certain areas of the web site. Most browsers are defaulted to accept and maintain cookies.  To learn more about cookies and how to specify your cookie preferences, please search for “cookie” in the “Help” portion of your browser. 

**Web Beacons**

In order to measure the effectiveness and/or traffic on our sites, our sites may use “pixel tags” (also called clear GIFs, web beacons, and web bugs) in conjunction with cookies.  A pixel tag is a type of web page graphic that often appears to be invisible because it is usually 1 by 1 pixel in size. The tag is used to track the number of users that arrive at our sites and their navigation through our sites. For instance, we may use a tag to statistically count the number of people using our site or particular pages within our site.     
We sometimes include pixel tags in our HTML-formatted e-mail messages that we send (or that are sent on our behalf) in order to determine which e-mail messages were opened and to note whether an e-mail message was acted upon. You may render some pixel tags or web beacons unusable by rejecting their associated cookies.    
We do not use the pixel tag technology to collect any personally identifiable information. 

**IP Addresses**

An Internet Protocol (IP) address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider (ISP) whenever you connect to the Internet. Like other Internet sites, MEDIAFREAKS PTE LTD may collect IP addresses to analyze aggregate information about the number of visitors and site usage. Your IP address is not linked with personal information that you provide. MEDIAFREAKS PTE LTD does reserve the right, however, to use IP addresses to identify individuals who threaten our site, service, or customers in accordance with regulatory requirements. 

**Other Features of Our Services**

Our sites may include various functionalities that are intended to serve you or help us better understand your needs.  For example, from time to time, we may ask for personally identifiable information when you complete a survey or enter a contest. In other circumstances we may offer you other web-enabled services such as newsletters, product information, and reminders.  When presenting you with such functionalities on our sites we will clearly describe the purpose for collecting such information, as well as the intended uses of the information. 

**Leaving MEDIAFREAKS PTE LTD**

As a resource to our visitors, we provide links to other web sites. We try to carefully choose those sites that we believe are useful and meet our high standards. However, we do not guarantee the standards of every web site to which we link, nor are we responsible for the content of non-MEDIAFREAKS PTE LTD sites. Links to external web sites are provided only for convenience and/or for informational purposes, and in no way constitute an endorsement.   
Please be aware that advertisers or third-party web sites that have links on our Web Sites may collect personally identifiable information from you. The information practices of those sites linked to us either through advertisements or other hyperlinks are not covered by this Privacy Policy. We suggest that when linking to another site, you always read the site’s privacy policy before volunteering any personally identifiable information on that site. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy may be revised periodically. By using this site you acknowledge our right to change this policy, without prior notification, and our commitment to post changes on this page so that you are informed of the types of information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, it is disclosed.  We will indicate on the Privacy Policy web page the date of the last Privacy Policy update.  We recommend that you visit our Privacy Policy page whenever you visit this Site so that you are aware of any changes. 

**The Privacy of Children**

MEDIAFREAKS PTE LTD’s web sites are not intended for children under the age of 13.  We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information online from visitors in this age group. 

**Contact Us**

If you have questions about this policy or MEDIAFREAKS PTE LTD's information collection, use, and disclosure practices, you may contact us at: 206A Syed Alwi Road, Singapore 207739. 

When you contact us, please note the name of the Web site or other online resource to which you inquiring, as well as the nature of the information about which you are inquiring.  We will use reasonable efforts to respond promptly to requests, questions or concerns you may have regarding our use of personal information about you. Except where required by law, MEDIAFREAKS PTE LTD cannot ensure a response to questions or comments regarding topics unrelated to this policy or MEDIAFREAKS PTE LTD's privacy practices. 

**Mediafreaks Blog**

As your supplementary read, we would like to invite you to visit the Mediafreaks [_Mediafreaks Blog_](http://articles.media-freaks.com/) , which exists to provide useful articles on animated-related subjects here - written for business marketers and 3D enthusiasts to pick up ideas on new media marketing and to understand more about the industry.

**Animation Showcase Site**

Also, we would like you to visit the Mediafreaks [_Animation Showcase Site_](http://showcase.media-freaks.com/) , which is a congregation of the finest animation clips we can find on the internet today. Ranging from animated TV commercials to animated shorts to medical animation, we would like this site to be a source of inspiration for you. We also encourage animators to submit their showreels as an avenue to showcase your work and portfolio. 

|   | 

|    
---  
  
Subscribe to Mediafreaks to receive updates on our projects, free articles and a useful free e-book! 

Read useful articles on animated-related subjects here - written for business marketers and 3D enthusiasts to pick up ideas on new media marketing and to understand more about the industry. Click above.   

We created a special animation showcase site that compiles the best and most interesting animation clips found on the internet for your viewing pleasure. You can also submit your clips here. Click above.   

**Copyright (C) 2003-2008, Mediafreaks Pte Ltd, Mediafreaks | 3D Animation**
